RG 005:038, Office of the Governor: Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. (1991-1995)
Connecticut State Library
Lowell P. Weicker, Jr. records
1977-1994,
bulk 1991-1994
1991-1994
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. Governor (1991-1995: Weicker)
79.75 cubic feet
Gov. Weicker's constituent correspondence, legal office files, press files, official statements, invitations accepted and regretted, subject files, and photographs.
RG005_038
Multiple
Biographical Note
Born: May 16, 1931, Paris, France.
College: Yale University, 1953, University of Virginia Law School, 1958.
Political Party: A Connecticut Party. Republican prior to 1990.
Offices: Connecticut General Assembly, House, 1963-1969 (R); First Selectman, Greenwich, 1964-1968 (R); U.S. Congress, 1969-1971 (R); U.S. Senate, 1971-1989 (R); Governor of Connecticut, 1991-1995 (ACP).
Lowell Palmer Weicker, Jr. was sworn in as Connecticut's 85th Governor on January 9, 1991, becoming the first independent Governor in the state since the Civil War. Weicker was born May 16, 1931 in Paris, France to Lowell P. and Mary Bickford Weicker. As a child, Weicker attended the Buckley School in New York City and Culver Military Academy in Culver, Indiana. In 1949 he graduated from the Lawrenceville School, a prep school in New Jersey. He went on to Yale where he developed an interest in politics, graduating in 1953 with a B.A. in political science.
Weicker served in the United States Army from 1953 to 1955 and in the Army Reserve from 1958 to 1964. He graduated from the University of Virginia Law School in 1958 and then moved to Greenwich, Connecticut where he helped found a law firm. As a Republican, he served as First Selectman of that town as well as a Representative to the Connecticut General Assembly.
In 1968 Weicker ran for and won a seat in the U.S. House of Representatives from the 4th District. During his one term in the House, he focused on urban renewal and transportation legislation and gained a reputation as a moderate conservative. Weicker won election to the U.S. Senate in 1970 after a split in the state Democratic Party resulted in a three-way race between Weicker, the Democratic nominee Joseph Duffy, and Thomas Dodd, who entered the race as an independent. The split in the Democratic vote gave Weicker the victory. While in the Senate, Weicker worked for passage of the War Powers Act, served on the Senate Watergate Committee, advocated oceanic research, and served on the Appropriations, Small Business, and Labor and Human Resources Committees. Weicker found himself at odds with the far right of the Republican Party over issues of school prayer, busing, and abortion. He also worked for health and education programs for physically and developmentally disabled persons and the poor. Weicker sponsored the Protection and Advocacy for the Mentally Ill Act in 1985 and in 1988 introduced legislation that would become the Americans with Disabilities Act. Weicker's independence led members of his own party to back his opponent Joseph Lieberman in the 1988 Senate race, causing Weicker's defeat.
Weicker then went to work for Research! America, a non-profit organization that raised public awareness about the benefits of medical research. He also taught a constitutional law course at the George Washington University Law School. It wasn't long before some of Weicker's friends began to urge him to seek the governorship of Connecticut. Ruling out a run as a Republican and believing the political atmosphere was right for a third-party candidate, Weicker entered the race and won under the A Connecticut Party that he founded. His opponents were Republican John Rowland and Democrat Bruce Morrison.
When Weicker entered office, the state's budget deficit was $963 million. During the campaign he had opposed an income tax but did not rule it out. Weicker asked William B. Cibes to become his budget director as head of the Office of Policy and Management. Cibes had sought the Democratic gubernatorial nomination but lost in a primary to Morrison because his platform included the creation of a state income tax. Cibes and his team developed three budget proposals, two that relied on the sales tax and one that included an income tax. Cibes convinced Weicker that an income tax was the only fiscally responsible choice. On February 13, 1991 Weicker unveiled a budget that proposed a flat income tax of 6 percent and a drop in the sales tax from 8 to 4.25 percent. During the next six months the General Assembly passed three no-income-tax budgets that continued the state's reliance on the sales tax. Weicker vetoed them all. For his part, Weicker proposed two other income-tax based budgets during that time. Stalemate resulted because the General Assembly did not have enough votes to override the vetoes or enough votes to pass an income tax. Both partries were split over the issue. Temporary spending authorizations kept the state running after the start of fiscal year 1992 except for a three day interruption starting on July 1. Finally on August 22, 1991 the General Assembly passed a budget that included a 4.5 percent flat income tax and a cut in the sales tax from 8 to 6 percent. Forty thousand people gathered at the state capitol in Hartford in protest on October 5, 1991. The income tax did take effect and the state ended fiscal year 1992 with a surplus of $110 million and continued in the black for the next two fiscal years.
The 1991 budget crises led to a standoff between Weicker and the state employee unions that supported his gubernatorial campaign. Wage concessions that some unions agreed to in April of 1991 had expired when the state started the new fiscal year without a budget. Without the concessions in place, some employees received scheduled wage increases at the start of the new fiscal year. Weicker asked the state employee unions to revive the April agreement. The unions wanted guaranteed job security in return. Without an agreement in place, thousands of state employees were either furloughed or laid off starting in November 1991, although some of the laid off employees would eventually be reinstated.
In addition to restructuring the revenue system, Weicker also implemented spending reforms and reorganized state government by consolidating agencies. Among the legislation he signed into law during his term were bills dealing with school desegregation, stricter gun control, and health care reform. Weicker's accomplishments during his first year as Governor led the John F. Kennedy Library Foundation to recognize him with the Profiles in Courage Award in 1992.
Weicker has three sons with his first wife Marie Louise "Bunny" Godfrey: Scott, Gray, and Brian and two sons with his second wife Camille Butler: Sonny and Lowell P. Weicker III, known as Tre. In December 1984 Weicker married his third wife Claudia Testa who has two sons: Mason and Andrew.
Bibliography
Congressional Quarterly's Guide to United States Elections. Washington, D.C.: Congressional Quarterly, 1994 [CSL call number GIS Ref JK 1967 .C662 1994.
Lieberman, Joseph. The Legacy, Connecticut Politics, 1930-1980. Hartford, Conn.: Spoonwood Press, 1981 [CSL call number JK 3395 .L53 1981].
Weicker, Lowell P., Jr. with Barry Sussman. Maverick: A Life in Politics. Boston, Mass.: Little, Brown and Company, 1995 [CSL call number E 840 .8 A43 1995].
Who’s Who in American Politics. Sixteenth Edition, 1997-1998. New Providence, N.J.: Marquis Who’s Who, 1997 [CSL call number E 176 .W6424].
Scope and Content
Gov. Weicker's constituent correspondence, legal office, press files, official statements, invitations accepted and rejected, subject files, and photographs. Constituent correspondence includes acknowledgements from the Governor to the correspondent, agency files containing letters referred to the appropriate agency for handling, and issue letters on a variety of topics. Press files contain press releases, speeches, appointments, bills signed, and veto messages. Legal office files contain auditor's reports, agency files, subject files, and special election files. A small accession related to inaugural activities has been added as addenda.
Arrangement
Series 1. Constituent Correspondence, 1987-1994, 54 cubic feet
Includes acknowledgements, agency files alphabetical by agency name, greeting, support, and thank you letters, issue letters arranged alphabetically, mag letters and miscellaneous letters.
Series 2. Press Files, 1991-1994, 5 cubic feet
Arranged chronologically.
Series 3. Official Statements, 1994, 1 cubit foot
Arranged chronologically.
Series 4. Invitations Accepted and Rejected, 1992-1993, 4 cubic feet
Arranged chronologically by event date.
Series 5. Legal Office, 1977-1994, 9.5 cubic feet
Includes auditor's reports, agency files, and subject files all arranged alphabetically, and special elections files arranged by office.
Series 6. Subject Files, 1986-1994, 2 cubic feet
Arranged alphabetically.
Series 7. Photographs, circa 1990-1993, 2 cubic feet
Unarranged.
Restricted, 1.5 cubic feet
Related Material
Lowell P. Weicker's Senate papers are at the Albert and Shirley Small Special Collections Library, University of Virginia.
Index Terms
Persons:
Weicker, Lowell, 1931-
Subjects:
Weicker, Lowell, 1931- -- Archives; Connecticut. Office of the Governor -- Archives; Connecticut -- History -- Sources; Connecticut -- Politics and government -- 1951- -- Sources; Governors -- Connecticut -- Archives; Income tax -- Connecticut
Document Types:
Correspondence; Photographs; Press releases; Proclamations; Records; Reports; Speeches
Restrictions on Access
Constituent correspondence is closed to researchers. These records may contain confidential personal data restricted by law. However, Box 24 that contains correspondence regarding the Department of Mental Health is open because original documents that contain confidential personal data have been removed and replaced with redacted copies. Please contact State Archives staff for assistance.
Gov. Weicker's records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Acquisition Information
Accession 2011-075 was transferred to the Connecticut State Library from the Lowell Weicker Papers at the Albert and Shirley Small Special Collections Library, University of Virginia in October 2010.
Container List
- Series 1. Constituent Correspondence, 1987-1994; 1995-040
  Constituent correspondence is closed to researchers. These records may contain confidential personal data restricted by law. However, Box 24 that contains correspondence regarding the Department of Mental Health is open because original documents that contain confidential personal data have been removed and replaced with redacted copies. Please contact State Archives staff for assistance.
  - Acknowledgements (Box 1)
    - 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1-6)
    - 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7-20)
    - 1993 (Box 2, Folder 1-12)
    - 1994 (Box 2, Folder 13-18)
  - Agency Files (Box 3)
    - Accountancy, Board of, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Accountancy, Board of, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Administrative Services, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3-12)
    - Administrative Services, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 13-23)
    - Administrative Services, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 1-5)
    - Administrative Services, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 6-7)
    - Aging, Commission of, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Aging, Dept. on, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 9-10)
    - Aging, Dept. on, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 11-12)
    - Aging, Dept. on, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Agriculture, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Agriculture, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 15-16)
    - Agriculture, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Agriculture, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Alcohol, Drug Abuse Commission, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 19-20)
    - Alcohol, Drug Abuse Commission, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Alcohol, Drug Abuse Commission, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Alcohol, Drug Abuse Commission, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Arts, Commission on the, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Arts, Commission on the, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Arts, Commission on the, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Arts, Commission on the, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Attorney General, Office of the State, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 28-30)
    - Attorney General, Office of the State, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
    - Attorney General, Office of the State, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3-5)
    - Attorney General, Office of the State, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 6-8)
    - Appropriations Committee, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Auditors of Public Accounts, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Auditors of Public Accounts, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Auditors of Public Accounts, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Banking, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 13-14)
    - Banking, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 15-18)
    - Banking, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 19-23)
    - Banking, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Bicentennial Commission of Connecticut, 1987-1991 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Blind, Board of Education and Services for the, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Blind, Board of Education and Services for the, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Blind, Board of Education and Services for the, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Blind, Board of Education and Services for the, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Bonding Commission, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Chief Medical Examiner, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Chief State's Attorney, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 32-34)
    - Chief State's Attorney, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - Chief State's Attorney, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 3-4)
    - Chief State's Attorney, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Child Support Enforcement Division, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
    - Child Support Enforcement Division, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 8-12)
    - Child Support Enforcement Division, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 13-18)
    - Child Support Enforcement Division, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 19-20)
    - Children and Families, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 21-22)
    - Children and Youth Services, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 23-28)
    - Children and Youth Services, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 1-6)
    - Children and Youth Services, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 7-10)
    - Claims Commissioner, Office of the, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Claims Commissioner, Office of the, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Claims Commissioner, Office of the, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Comptroller, Office of the State, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Comptroller, Office of the State, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 15-16)
    - Comptroller, Office of the State, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Comptroller, Office of the State, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Connecticut Housing Finance Authority, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Connecticut Housing Finance Authority, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Connecticut Housing Finance Authority, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Connecticut Resources Recovery Authority, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Connecticut Service Corps, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Consumer Counsel, Office of, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Consumer Protection, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 25-31)
    - Consumer Protection, Dept. of, A-L, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 32-35)
    - Consumer Protection, Dept. of, M-Z, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
    - Consumer Protection, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 4-7)
    - Consumer Protection, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 8-9)
    - Correction, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 10-23)
    - Correction, Dept. of, A-F, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 24-27)
    - Correction, Dept. of, G-Z, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 1-10)
    - Correction, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 11-21)
    - Correction, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 22-23)
    - Correction, Dept. of: Sentence Review Division, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Deaf and Hearing Impaired, Commission on, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Deaf and Hearing Impaired, Commission on, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Deaf and Hearing Impaired, Commission on, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Disabilities, Office of Protection and Advocacy for Persons with, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Disabilities, Office of Protection and Advocacy for Persons with, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Disabilities, Office of Protection and Advocacy for Persons with, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Disabilities, Office of Protection and Advocacy for Persons with, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 1-12)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 13-24)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of, A-F, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 25-30)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of, G-Z, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 1-11)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 12-18)
    - Education, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 19-32)
    - Education, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 1-10)
    - Education, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 11-20)
    - Education, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 21-22)
    - Education, U.S. Dept. of, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Education, U.S. Dept. of, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Emergency Management, Office of, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Emergency Management, Office of, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Emergency Management, Office of, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Environmental Protection, Dept. of, A-E, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 28-34)
    - Environmental Protection, Dept. of, F-Z, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 1-20)
    - Environmental Protection, Dept. of, A-G, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 21-29)
    - Environmental Protection, Dept. of, H-Z, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1-15)
    - Environmental Protection, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 16-27)
    - Environmental Protection, Dept. of, A-L, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 28-31)
    - Environmental Protection, Dept. of, M-Z, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 1-3)
    - Environmental Protection, Dept. of, Clean air, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Environmental Protection, Dept. of, Clean water / Long Island Sound, 1992, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Environmental Protection, Dept. of, News clippings, reports, printed material, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Environmental Protection, Dept. of, Recycling, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Ethics Commission, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Ethics Commission, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Ethics Commission, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Freedom of Information Commission, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Freedom of Information Commission, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Freedom of Information Commission, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Freedom of Information Commission, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Government Reorganization, Commission to Effect, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Health Services, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 16-31)
    - Health Services, Dept. of, A-L, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 32-38)
    - Health Services, Dept. of, M-Z, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 1-4)
    - Higher Education, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 5-7)
    - Higher Education, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 8-12)
    - Higher Education, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 13-15)
    - Higher Education, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 16-17)
    - Historical Commission, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Historical Commission, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Historical Commission, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Historical Commission, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Hospitals and Health Care, Commission on, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Hospitals and Health Care, Commission on, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 23-24)
    - Hospitals and Health Care, Commission on, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Hospitals and Health Care, Commission on, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Housing, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 27-32)
    - Housing, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 1-8)
    - Housing, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 9-14)
    - Housing, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 15-16)
    - Housing and Urban Development, U.S. Dept. of, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Human Resources, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 18-24)
    - Human Resources, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 25-31)
    - Human Resources, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 1-3)
    - Human Resources, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Human Rights and Opportunities, Commission on, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 5-7)
    - Human Rights and Opportunities, Commission on, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 8-12)
    - Human Rights and Opportunities, Commission on, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 13-15)
    - Human Rights and Opportunities, Commission on, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 16-17)
    - Human Rights and Opportunities, Commission on, Indian Affairs, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Human Rights and Opportunities, Commission on, Indian Affairs, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Human Rights and Opportunities, Commission on, Indian Affairs, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 20-22)
    - Human Rights and Opportunities, Commission on, Indian Affairs, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Income Maintenance, Dept. of, A-F, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 24-27)
    - Income Maintenance, Dept. of, G-Z, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 1-10)
    - Income Maintenance, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 11-26)
    - Insurance Dept., 1991 (Box 20, Folder 1-7)
    - Insurance Dept., 1992 (Box 20, Folder 8-17)
    - Insurance Dept., 1993 (Box 20, Folder 18-23)
    - Insurance Dept., 1994 (Box 20, Folder 24-26)
    - Interior, U.S. Dept. of the, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Judicial Dept., 1991 (Box 21, Folder 2-11)
    - Judicial Dept., 1992 (Box 21, Folder 12-21)
    - Judicial Dept., A-H, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 22-28)
    - Judicial Dept., I-Z, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 1-5)
    - Judicial Dept., 1994 (Box 22, Folder 6-8)
    - Labor, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 9-13)
    - Labor, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 14-24)
    - Labor, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 1-7)
    - Labor, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 8-11)
    - Labor, Dept. of, Unemployment Compensation, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 12-13)
    - Labor, Dept. of, Unemployment Compensation, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 14-17)
    - Labor, Dept. of, Unemployment Compensation, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 18-20)
    - Labor, U.S. Dept. of, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Legislative Management, Joint Commission on, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Library, Connecticut State, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 23-25)
    - Library, Connecticut State, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 26-28)
    - Library, Connecticut State, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Library, Connecticut State, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Liquor Control, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Liquor Control, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Liquor Control, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Liquor Control, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Mental Health, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 1-7)
    - Mental Health, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 8-12)
    - Mental Health, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 13-23)
    - Mental Health, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 24-25)
    - Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 1-10)
    - Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 11-17)
    - Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 18-22)
    - Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 23-24)
    - Military Dept., 1991 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Military Dept., 1992 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Military Dept., 1993 (Box 25, Folder 27-28)
    - Military Dept., 1994 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 1-14)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, A-L, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 15-29)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, M-Z, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 1-11)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 12-25)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 26-28)
    - Pardons, Board of, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 1-6)
    - Pardons, Board of, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 7-8)
    - Pardons, Board of, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 9-10)
    - Pardons, Board of, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 11-13)
    - Parole, Board of, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 14-17)
    - Parole, Board of, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Parole, Board of, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Policy and Management, Office of, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 20-29)